Charlotte Clark

Los Angeles, CA 90025 • 623 236 6390 • charlotte.clark@alumni.usc.edu

https://charlotteclark.io/

https://github.com/charlocc

https://www.linkedin.com/in/charlotte-clark-ba486213a/

SUMMARY

Skilled full-stack web developer with 2+ years of experience in marketing and social media for a behavioral health provider, a role which requires a broad approach to problem solving and ability to work collaboratively with a team.

SKILLS & INTERESTS

Languages: JavaScript, HTML, CSS

Proficient in: Node.js, Express.js, Handlebars.js, React.js, bcrypt, Heroku, Mysql2, Adobe Suite, Wordpress

RECENT PROJECTS

Activity Planner – Find campgrounds and national parks near you

Aug. 2021 https://charlocc.github.io/activityplanner/

• Team Project: I connected two APIs and set up local storage, as well as the front-end javascript **#bigtechblog** – A blog for discussing everything tech-related,

Sept. 2021 https://radiant-ocean-47580.herokuapp.com/

• MVC framework, demonstrates Handlebars.js, Heroku, Express.js, bcrypt

Platformer Explorer – A cute platformer world to explore, move your character using the arrow keys

Jan. 2022 https://charlocc.github.io/platformer/

• This site uses object collision detection and a fixed time step loop to run the game

WORK EXPERIENCE

Pyles and Associates – Los Angeles, CA

2019 - Present

- **Web Developer** (2021-Present)
 - o Design, create, and maintain website for the company using wordpress
 - o Consult on app development project
- Marketing Manager (2020 Present)
 - o Track weekly analytics and develop strategies to grow on-line audience
 - Create content for all platforms including Instagram, Facebook, Youtube, LinkedIn, and GoogleMyBusiness
 - o Lead marketing team meetings and coordinate content creation
- Senior Therapist (2019 2021)
 - O Conduct monthly evaluations and trainings with junior behavior technicians
 - O Support program managers by troubleshooting barriers to client and staff skill acquisition
 - o Implement behavioral support plans for children with developmental disabilities

Expeditors International of Washington – Air Export Intern, *Los Angeles, CA*

2018

· Scheduled and coordinated international freight by air

Hurry Curry of Tokyo – Waitress, Seattle, WA

2017

EDUCATION

University of California, Los Angeles

2021

The Full Stack Coding Bootcamp Certificate at UCLA Extension

University of Southern California, Dornsife College of Letters Arts, and Sciences

2016-2020